Finding Aid for Caroline Bartlett Crane addresses and other printed items, 1889-1922
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Caroline Bartlett Crane addresses and other printed items 1889-1922
Crane, Caroline Bartlett, 1858-1935.
1 box
749 DA 2; C891.2; A227
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was drawn together from different sources.
No further additions to the collection are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Caroline Bartlett Crane was a Kalamazoo, Michigan Unitarian minister.
This collection of published addresses and other items of Caroline Bartlett Crane was accumulated from different sources.
- Various printed items
  - Kalamazoo, Mich. First Unitarian Church
    - Calendar for December 1892 (Box 1)
    - Calendar for May 1893 (Box 1)
    - Calendar for February 1894 (Box 1)
    - Calendar for November 1894 (Box 1)
  - Kalamazoo United Club
    - First Annual, Banquet, May 2, 1890 (Box 1)
    - Third Annual Banquet, May 24, 1892 (Box 1)
    - Season of 1889-1890, First year (Box 1)
    - Season of 1891-1892, The Third year (Box 1)
  - People's Church of Kalamazoo, Mich. Calendar for December 1895 (Box 1)
  - The Peoples Church of Kalamazoo, Mich.
    - Annual 1897 (Box 1)
    - Condensed Program, Calendar of Meetings, 1896-1897 (Box 1)
    - Calendar February, 1898 (Box 1)
    - Calendar April, 1898 (Box 1)
- Addresses
  - Address before New Hampshire State Conference of Charities and Corrections. Portsmouth. May 1, 1908 (Box 1)
  - The Charities Organization of Kalamazoo, Michigan. December 1, 1907 (Box 1)
  - Christmas! Undated, 2 copies (Box 1)
  - "Clean Meat for Philadelphia." City Club Bulletin. March 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - "Clean Streets for Chicago." Address delivered at Fullerton Hall, Art Institute, Chicago. November 10, 1907 (Box 1)
  - Constitution and By-laws of the Women's Civic Improvement League. Kalamazoo, Michigan (Box 1)
  - "Carry On" Official publication of The Women's Committee (Michigan division) Council of National Defense. Kalamazoo, Mich. November 23, 1918 (Box 1)
  - "Communications", Read to board of supervisors of Kalamazoo, Co. March 10, 1908 (Box 1)
  - "Co-operation with State Boards of Health", An address on "President's Evening"-General Federation of Women's Clubs. San Francisco July 5, 1912 (Box 1)
  - "The Cow and The Baby"-The Woman Citizen. December, 1925 (Box 1)
  - "Does Your Town need a Mr. Ward?"-The Woman Citizen. February, 1926 (Box 1)
  - "The Forgotten People"-Address given at Abraham Lincoln Center, Chicago. May 24, 1908 (Box 1)
  - "Forty Questions on The Life of Jesus"-Arranged for The First Unitarian Sunday School of Kalamazoo. May 1894 (Box 1)
  - General Sanitary Survey of Erie, Pennsylvania. June 1, 1910 (Box 1)
  - General Sanitary Survey of Nashville, Tenn. May 7, 1910 (Box 1)
  - History of The Work of The Women's Committee (Michigan division) (Box 1)
  - Council of National Defense During The War. June, 1922 (Box 1)
  - "The Housewife and the Marketing Problem." Reprinted from the National Municipal Review, Philadelphia, July 1918 (Box 1)
  - "How Civic Society's Wood Yard Gives Work to Kalamazoo's Needy" undated (Box 1)
  - State Conference on Increased Food Production and Registration for War Service. Lansing, Michigan. March 12-13, 1918 (Box 1)
  - "Investigation Preceding Relief in Charity Organization Work." undated (Box 1)
  - "Is it any of our Business?" Kalamazoo, Michigan. April 10, 1908 (Box 1)
  - Letters on Civic Improvement-V-Back Yard Sanitation (Box 1)
  - Letters on Civic Improvement-III-Farming in The City (Box 1)
  - "Municipal Housekeeping." Reprinted from "Proceedings" of Baltimore City-.Wide Congress March 8-10, 1911 (Box 1)
  - "Our Problems of the Poorhouse." The Commons. April, 1905 (Box 1)
  - Report on Almshouses of Charities and Corrections Committee of Michigan State Federation of Women's Clubs. October 22, 1908? (Box 1)
  - Report on Conditions Found at our County Almshouse. Kalamazoo, undated (Box 1)
  - Sanitary Survey of Saginaw, Michigan, 1911 (Box 1)
  - Sanitary Survey of Uniontown, Pennsylvania, 1914 (Box 1)
  - Savings Collections Under the Charity Organization, undated (Box 1)
  - "The School Plant as a Public Health Asset." July, 1913 (Box 1)
    (Reprinted from the Proceedings of the National Education Association. Philadelphia. Penn.)
  - "Small Town Tenements". The Woman Citizen. August 8, 1925 (Box 1)
  - A Study and Some Suggestions Concerning Christmas Dinners for the Poor. Kalamazoo, undated (Box 1)
  - "The Sunday School." Western Unitarian Sunday School Society. Chicago. December 1897 (Box 1)
  - "U.S. Inspected and Passed." Reprinted from The Survey. New YorkSeptember 6, 1913, 2 copies (Box 1)
  - "The Ultimate Reason for The Hope That is in Us." undated (Box 1)
    (Reprinted from The Reform Advocate Bloch & Newman, Publ. Chicago.)
  - "The Visiting Nurse of The Women's Civic Improvement League of Kalamazoo." undated (Box 1)
  - "The Work for Clean Streets" Kalamazoo, undated (Box 1)
  - "With The Visiting Nurse Among The Poor and Sick of Kalamazoo, undated (Box 1)
  - "The Work of The General Secretary of The Charities Organization." Kalamazoo, Mich. January 12, 1908 (Box 1)